##### Speedify LIVE Office Hours

twitch

Updated: October 27, 2022

Privacy Policy
==============

Connectify cares about your privacy
===================================

Your privacy and information security are as important to us as they are to you. Connectify’s Privacy Policy explains exactly what data we gather, and how we process it. We are only interested in gathering enough data to provide the service to you, and to tune Speedify's performance to be the fastest, most reliable VPN in the world. If you have any questions please email us at: [\[email protected\]](https://speedify.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Thanks,  
Alex Gizis  
CEO

The short version
=================

* Connectify meets all the requirements of the GDPR.
* Connectify collects the minimal amount of information that is needed to give you fast, reliable, secure communication.
* Connectify does NOT track the websites you visit, the data you exchange, or anything related to your DNS requests.
* Connectify does not share ANY personal information with third parties.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
===============================

When you use our website to learn about our services, we store your IP address, the type of browser you are using, the pages you access, and your operating system. All data is stored on an anonymous basis. We use this information so that we can display our website pages on your computer or mobile device.

At the time you purchase a Speedify subscription, you provide us with your name and email address. We need this information so that we can create your account, and give you permission to access the services you subscribed to. Your billing information is provided directly to Fastspring, Recurly, or Stripe payment services, and is not available to us. For more information, please see [Fastspring’s privacy policy](https://fastspring.com/privacy/), [Recurly's privacy policy](https://recurly.com/legal/privacy), and [Stripe's privacy policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).

When you use Speedify to communicate over the Internet we receive your IP address and Device ID. We also record at what time each connection begins, how long each connection lasts, and the amount of data used. We use this information to provide you with a connection, troubleshoot issues, and improve performance.

If you contact us for support, we will need your email address so that we can respond to you. If you wish, you may also provide us with your name (this is optional).

HOW DOES CONNECTIFY PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY?
=========================================

We have no record of the websites that you visit. We do not retain any of the data that you send or receive while using our services. All of that information vanishes from our systems as soon as it is transmitted.

The personal information that we receive from you when communicating using Speedify is automatically deleted after six months.

Our backend servers and databases are encrypted and firewalled. Those servers are located in the United States in physically secure facilities with restricted access.

We do not provide any personal information to third parties.

We do not provide governments with access to our data (unless we are required to by law).

COOKIES
=======

View our [Cookie Policy](https://speedify.com/cookie-policy/).

GDPR AND DATA PROCESSING
========================

To the extent that Connectify processes any personal data that is subject to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), on the user’s behalf, in the provision of the Service, the terms of [Connectify's Data Processing Agreement](https://speedify.com/data-processing-agreement/) and [Standard Contractual Clauses](https://speedify.com/standard-contractual-clauses/) which are hereby incorporated by reference, shall apply.

WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS?
=====================

You can ask us to give you a copy of personal data that we have.

You can ask us to correct any personal data that is inaccurate. You can also ask us to delete any personal information that we do not need to maintain your subscription. You can ask us to delete all of your personal information (if you are ending your subscription), and we will do so without undue delay.

You can ask us to transfer your personal data to another company.

If you are in the European Union, you can lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority, or the Irish Data Protection Commissioner who we have designated as our lead supervisory authority in the European Union. The address is:

Irish Data Protection Commissioner  
Office of the Data Protection Commissioner  
Canal House, Station Road, Portarlington, Co. Laois, R32 AP23, Ireland  
Phone +353 57 868 4757  
Fax: +353 57 868 4757  
Email: [\[email protected\]](https://speedify.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

If you are a California resident, please see our [CCPA Privacy Policy](https://speedify.com/privacy-policy-ccpa/)

HOW DO WE UPDATE OUR PRIVACY POLICY?
====================================

By making changes on this website page, and indicating the effective date on the top of the document. In some cases, we may send you a notification by email if you are a current subscriber. If you do not accept the changes to our privacy policy, please let us know and we will close your account.

DO WE HAVE ANY AGE LIMITS FOR THE USE OF OUR SERVICES?
======================================================

Yes, we do. If you are under age 16, then you are not permitted to use our services. If you learn that someone under the age of 16 has opened an account with us, please let us know so we can close the account and delete their personal information.

HOW DO YOU CONTACT US?
======================

###### For Privacy Questions:

[\[email protected\]](https://speedify.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

###### For Other Questions:

[\[email protected\]](https://speedify.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

###### Mailing Address:

Connectify, Inc.  
601 Spring Garden, 3rd floor  
Philadelphia, PA 19123

Multiple connections. Maximum performance.
==========================================

Speedify is the only app that combines all of your Internet connections to keep you online when it matters most.

Upcoming Events
---------------

Nov 6

10:00 am - 11:00 am EST

### [11/06 @ 10am EST – How do you BOND more than two internet connections? | Ask the CEO your tech questions](https://speedify.com/event/11-06-10am-est-how-do-you-bond-more-than-two-internet-connections-ask-the-ceo-your-tech-questions/ "11/06 @ 10am EST – How do you BOND more than two internet connections? | Ask the CEO your tech questions")

Nov 13

10:00 am - 11:00 am EST

### [11/13 @ 10am EST – How do you put Speedify on your router? | Ask the CEO your tech questions](https://speedify.com/event/11-13-10am-est-how-do-you-put-speedify-on-your-router-ask-the-ceo-your-tech-questions/ "11/13 @ 10am EST – How do you put Speedify on your router? | Ask the CEO your tech questions")

#### Popular Posts

* [\[SOLVED\] Mobile Hotspot Connected but No Internet](https://speedify.com/blog/fix-slow-internet/mobile-hotspot-connected-but-no-internet-fix/)
* [\[TUTORIAL\] Snapchat Unblocked at School - How to Guide](https://speedify.com/blog/how-to/snapchat-unblocked-at-school-tutorial/)

### Bonding Apps

* * *

### Technology

* * *

### SOLUTIONS

* * *

### Company

* * *

Follow us!

This website uses cookies. To learn more, visit our [Cookie Policy](https://speedify.com/cookie-policy)[Ok](#)
